[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            1
        ],
        "question": "What is the main difference between the model in this notebook and the one in the previous lesson?",
        "answer": "This notebook uses a simpler matrix factorization model, while the previous lesson used a deep neural net model.",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            2
        ],
        "question": "What does the dot product of two vectors return?",
         "answer": "A single scalar number",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
          2
        ],
        "question": "For the dot product to be defined between two vectors, what should be true about their lengths?",
         "answer": "The vectors must be of the same length.",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            3
        ],
         "question": "According to the intuitive interpretation, what does the user vector tell about?",
        "answer": "'how does this user feel about action?'. Do they love it? Hate it? Or are they indifferent?",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
           5
        ],
        "question": "What are the columns used from ratings.csv file?",
        "answer": "userId, movieId, rating, y",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
   },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
           5
        ],
         "question": "What are the columns used from movie.csv file?",
        "answer": "movieId, title",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            7
        ],
         "question": "What is the shape of the embedded matrix after the PCA?",
        "answer": "(4790, 3)",
        "task": "Principal Component Analysis",
        "skill": "Kernel PCA"
    },
        {
        "cell_ids": [
             9
        ],
        "question": "What is the size of the embedding vector for users and movies in the matrix factorization model?",
         "answer":"8",
        "task":"Recommendation Systems",
       "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
           10
        ],
        "question": "What is the loss function used to train the matrix factorization model?",
       "answer": "MSE",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            10
        ],
        "question": "What is the evaluation metric used to train the matrix factorization model?",
         "answer": "MAE",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    }
]